Good evening, Insomniacs.
Tonight's forecast, 100% chance of scre-
Tonight, thought I'd get some peace for rest.
Then a six foot island shoulder pass, said psych, you're our guest.
Skeleton drove a limousine, made entire of cheese,
while Ronald Reagan surfed a tornado.
Through a forest full of bees
A payphone rang
Soup
Then fifty
Haunted mall from 985
Was floating
No space
Ghost leader rose
And struck
Visible face
It's the escalators on player
Boffman cooking breakfast
Aliens filing taxes
Haunted game show
Nobody wins
But the channel changes you
Hello to nobody that's fine. Well, I see what's going on. I mean, it's like you got, you know, big biscuits, beta. Oh, Arthur. Oh, you can't go to psych. Yeah, you can't go to psych. So beta, I guess beta and Sam and they're in charge of everybody. I guess Kate too, you know, they're I guess they're just the big.
I mean, it's like a huge amount of them.
There's some cool people, a few.
They're very far in between.
They're basically just a bunch of monkeys, you know.
But anyway, okay.
So anyway, yeah, they want to say,
oh, don't come to my show.
Oh, but they don't watch,
but oh, but they watch every minute of it.
I mean, she's like, oh, I saw every minute Arthur.
You know what I mean?
We're not allowed over there, Arthur.
Arthur's like what and then she's like, well, did you hear what they said about salmon?
You know, do you hear the shit that's talked about me in every single shot and you're and she's like well
You're supposed to say you're never go there again. Oh my god
dumb bitch
I mean honestly, you should have been named be charge. You really should have
Just fits your your mental capacity so much better
But I guess people just like retards. I mean, it's just like, you know, I used to like those shows like, you know those
Down with the the family whatever it's like, you know much of Down syndrome people
I mean that's what it's like over there, and he you know
Branden didn't have a right when he's like listening to like the show last night. Oh
Oh shout out God
God, okay. How about then either? Oh, RIP to you know, Gea. Lovely, you know
You don't have anything to say except shout out and RIP
and shaloo-loo, and oh my God, and it'd be like,
I mean, I tried to listen to it a little bit,
and it, like, I've hit me, and he starts to sing,
and it's just, like, so sad that I can't handle it,
so I have to turn it off.
Okay, I'm gonna put on my, really,
I'm just going for, like, a little walk.
Let's see, what's my help?
I'll put my link up.
I don't know, the world, the world just goes crazy.
Alexander's now.
No glazing over Q again.
I mean, it's like,
jeez, Louise.
Can I get some stability with somebody?
I mean, it's gonna be a love with Q the next day.
I don't know.
Seems just a little weird, but anyway.
So I think I'll start saying,
I'll start saying not to go to people's chat.
I mean, should I start like, you know, intimidating Maya?
The chat seems to be fine when being intimidated.
Not my chat usually, but their chat's all do. Oh that horrible he-man
Animal abuser. Oh, and he's a pdf and he has a pdf on his show
Okay, so now that's like legally me at lip again legally actionable slander. No proof
right
Miss using terms actually hurting children actually by using those kind of terms when they don't apply
Because then that just cheapens the term
I mean, they're actually giving power to the PDFs.
I mean, isn't that weird?
They're doing exactly the opposite
of what they're saying they're against.
They're promoting as all they could talk about.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't know.
And it's like, most of these people don't even have kids.
I mean, I kind of take more seriously now, right?
I mean,
I can do one thing.
I don't know, it's like my dad was like,
I think like 39, my mom was 29 when they married.
Is that pedophilia now?
I mean, it's like, I mean, really,
I mean, it's just gotten so stupid.
Something that I'm not even sure.
I mean, I can almost agree with Alexandra.
Is this just like a smoke screen
being thrown up to like distract people from something?
Yes, not my, not a meth gang
or any kind of operation I have.
It's the cover of their own.
Disgusting behavior blaming it on other people or trying to make it. It's called narcissism. It's called leveling
Or you just you level like this disgusting charge, and then that makes you look higher because you know
Well, you might have done something bad, but they are worse
And so they're a bad person now and you're a good person again, and you can just be like a good person for
strangers
But don't even exist
Yeah, I mean it's like most of these people just don't even exist in your mouth
It exists in your mind is these people in the shadows and these streamers and oh my god
Poor people I mean just like slander slander slander people come in suicide over these things and then it's like and then you guys celebrate
Oh my gosh. Well, they take themselves out. You know good. That's the try
I mean on my show the trash takes itself out. That means people don't come but in your life that means
They commit suicide I mean there's so much suicide beating. It's like straight out suicide beating. You say I'm suicide beating, right?
Hmm. There's no idea. These people are capable of
Hi, can I get you Swisher, please?
My bag, thank you so much. Thank you
I'm gonna go get a coffee at McDonald's
Anyway, so I know I understand if you're like you're probably like a lot of people are just afraid
There's afraid of beta
Like oh my god beat will talk about me or you know, or you know them or in a bad way or don't be allowed to beat his chat
And so much like that's the thing. It's like there are so many lonely people and it's like I guess I'm not like enough
So like, you know
Here's the ones lonely to see it to sit a bunch sit around with a bunch of monkeys. It's like they're at the zoo and
You know that cures our loneliness. I mean, I just watch it because I like to go to the zoo
I know they're monkeys. I don't get in the fucking cages with the monkeys
Okay, well, I went to McDonald's.
I got my data today, got my drinks,
and we're so friendly.
And, look, my whole bill is paid.
You can see no one's chasing after me today.
Just what the surface is.
Not a lot of people can do that.
That's why I do like some people in my chat.
But they're pretty much, you know,
they've been rendered, you know, scared.
So it's okay.
Don't be scared, or worse, they're just, like, you know,
secretly fapping to my show.
Like, no.
I know some of these guys have a crush on me.
I think I'm a sex pest.
You should see the messages I get from some of these guys.
Wow.
I'm actually like...
I'm like the doctor Ruth of the community.
She did? Oh, that's great.
She donated $1,000 because she wants to be friends
or what's going on. I don't understand.
Congratulations.
Well, I just want to make clear I never asked her for a penny.
I never demanded anything.
I was just grateful for whatever was gifted, you know?
I didn't even publicize them or anything, you know?
But congratulations.
I guess your internship, she's chosen you back for the internship.
But I guess what will happen is what always happens
is like everyone else will just join up and be friends
and then hate me.
I mean, that's like, that's like the pretty much the MO, right?
That's what's usual is, so I'm used to that.
Unfortunately, the, my coupons for the coffee, I guess they use the last night or something like that.
I have to go get my, I have a coffee at home from the bagel store.
Well, congratulations, Brandy Q for the thousand dollars.
Yeah, I guess you found your cash out.
Yeah, but Brighton Q.
Brighton Q does a great imitation of Sam Man, though.
He's just, he's how dumb he is.
I mean, Sam Man is like, literally,
literally it's like everyone loves Sam Man
the same reason everyone likes
that the guy corp-y from Life Goes On, you know?
Who's like a red-headed ginger, right?
With Down syndrome.
But oh, but he's like so,
kind of just so dumb that...
But pure in a certain way because he's just so dumb. He doesn't even know and then it's like some people say, oh
Kind of like a like a baby. It's like, you know
right
But he's not he's a oh and then he's saying wash your ass. I mean, have you seen this guy on it?
He's he's in his like, you know, his wife beater. That's like three sizes too small, right?
felt stained
It's big big his big
you know, buckwheat in a headlock armpit,
you know, stinking.
He's got the empty fish tank behind him.
His chair looks like it's made out of rubber bands and hope.
I mean, he's sitting there.
We already know his table is, like,
one of those, like, picnic, fold-up picnic tables
that's fallen. It's literally collapsed on the show.
And we've all heard, like, you know, his dad and his brother.
His brother is this weirdo.
Tied some guy up on his air mattress.
That's why it's topped.
Oh, my gosh.
I mean, they're just so sick.
Okay, well, anyway, I had a great walk with you guys.
That was a fun walk.
Thanks for the comment, Brandon.
Yeah, so, as for the rest of you that are like,
Oh, my God, this doesn't have the words in the chat.
They're sitting in the chat.
Okay.
Three re-charts.
Go back to salmon. Stay there. Go to beat us. Stay there. Don't come back to it
I don't want I don't like most of you. I hate actually. I hate most of you
I like a certain amount of people the ones that are like, you know, I have intelligence heart
mind like some something more than just
shallow
idiocy paranoia
Gossip hate bullying. I mean and look you had that you had, you know, reality Nancy was in the community
you know, supporting pretty much everyone.
So nice, I never saw her be mean to anybody.
Like never saw her be mean to anybody, you know?
I even got mad at her a couple of times.
I'm like, well, why is she like, you know,
joking about me with them?
And like, yeah, but that's like,
I mean, she's allowed to do that.
But look, but looking with her, but she's done down.
Now she's a, according to them,
now she's some kind of predator, protector, right?
And then Vita, Vita got jealous over, you know?
thinking that thing that is was talking to her personally
and blocked her and now slanders her everywhere she goes.
I mean, it's like kind of the saddest thing.
So I'm sorry, Nancy,
and I want you guys to know that Nancy tonight
will have her own stream on this topic
of the bullies in the community.
So you can see for yourself,
from a perspective of an insider,
really what's really going on here.
And you know what, shame on a lot of you
for just being such followers and you're sad.
And, you know, I'm kind of ashamed to know
or be associated with some of you.
You know, this is not, like, the core fan base of the show
and talking about these, like, these peripheral people
that should never have been around in the first place.
And so I apologize for that.
I'll be back. Thank you, guys, for having at least an open mind.
While I talk, check out my community wall.
There is a contest right now for a beautiful card.
One of many coming out, these are gorgeous.
You can see my thumbnail, you can see the style,
get the idea, and they're tradeable.
They also are used for divination,
so you can collect a whole deck and use yourself.
Okay, let me get night guys for a good day.
I'll be back later.